destructuring assignment take values from arrays or properties from objects
解构赋值从数组或对象的属性中获取值
and set them as local variables it's a technique that
并将它们设置为局部变量，这是一种
can make your javascript code more concise and readable
可以使您的 javascript 代码更简洁和易读的技术
imagine you have an array and you want to assign some of its values to local
假设您有一个数组并且您想将其一些值分配给局部
variables one option is to assign each variable by
变量一个选项是 通过
referencing its index in the array that works fine but it's not very
引用数组中的索引来分配每个变量可以正常工作，但是解构不是很
elegant with destructuring we can do the same thing with a single line of code
优雅我们可以
by using brackets after const we can assign a variable name
通过在 const 之后使用括号来用一行代码做同样的事情我们可以
to each index in the array the position of the variable name
为数组中的每个索引分配一个变量名变量名的位置
matches the values index in the array the syntax may look familiar to you if
与数组中的值索引匹配如果您曾经使用过 react 的语法可能看起来很熟悉，
you've ever used react which relies on destructuring for the used state hook
它依赖于对已用状态挂钩的解构
when working with arrays you may want to emit a variable which you can do by
在使用数组时您可能想要发出一个可以执行的变量 通过
adding a comma without a variable name to skip that index
添加一个没有变量名的逗号来跳过该索引，
in other cases you might want to name the first couple variables
在其他情况下，您可能想要命名前几个变量，
then put the remainder in their own array that can be achieved by putting
然后将其余变量放在他们自己的可以通过
three dots in front of the variable name you might also want to set a default
在变量名前面放置三个点来实现的数组您可能还想设置一个默认
value in case the value in the array is undefined use the equal sign to provide
值以防数组中的值未定义 使用等号
the fallback value in addition to arrays destructuring also
提供备用值 除了数组解构也
applies to objects notice how we're duplicating the
适用于 对象注意到我们如何通过在 const 后面加上大括号来将
object's property name as a variable with dot notation
对象的属性名称复制为带有点符号
by putting braces after const you can reference property names which will
的变量，您可以引用属性名称，这些属性名称将
automatically become local variables which is much cleaner than referencing
自动成为局部变量，这比
them line by line with dot notation and just like arrays you can use the
使用点符号逐行引用它们要干净得多，就像数组一样 您可以使用
equal sign to set a default value but in some cases you may want to use a
等号设置默认值，但在某些情况下，您可能希望使用与对象本身
different name than what's provided on the object itself
提供的名称不同的名称
adding a colon after the property name allows you to rename it which is
，在属性名称后添加一个冒号允许您重命名它，这
especially useful when dealing with name collisions or when working with objects
在处理名称时特别有用碰撞或在
that use property names that are not valid variable names
使用属性名称不是有效变量名称的对象时
in addition to renaming you can also use a colon to access
，除了重命名之外，您还可以使用 冒号访问
nested properties or in other words set a variable from an object within an
嵌套属性，或者换句话说，从对象中的对象设置变量
object in addition to destructuring top level
除了解构顶级
variables you can also use the syntax in for loops
变量之外，您还可以使用 for 循环中的语法，
which is awesome when you have an array of objects when working with functions
当您使用函数时拥有对象数组时，这非常棒
you can destructure arrays and objects passed as arguments
解构作为参数传递的数组和对象，
providing yet another way to obliterate unnecessary lines of javascript from
提供另一种从代码库中删除不必要的 javascript 行的方法
your code base this has been destructuring assignment
这已经
in javascript in 100 seconds make sure to hit the like button it
在 100 秒内解构 javascript 中的赋值确保点击“like”按钮 它
really helps out these short videos thanks for watching and if you want to
确实有助于这些短视频感谢观看，如果 你
learn more hang out for a minute while we go over a few more advanced tricks
想了解更多，在我们讨论一些更高级的技巧时
that you may not know about one thing that array destructuring
，你可能不知道数组解构
enables is variable swapping without the need for an intermediate variable it
启用的一件事是变量交换，而不需要中间变量，它
doesn't come up often in javascript but it is a useful thing to know for
在 javascript 中不经常出现 但是对于
computer science in general normally to swap two variables you need
计算机科学来说，通常交换两个变量是有用的，你需要
a temporary variable because once the first variable is reassigned you lose
一个临时的 v  ariable，因为一旦第一个变量被重新分配，你就会失去
its value but with a radius structuring we have
它的值，但是使用半径结构，我们有
the syntax available to perform a swap without the need for the intermediate
可用的语法来执行交换，而不需要中间
variable use destructuring to reassign the values
变量使用解构
by putting the original two in an array but in reverse order you'll
通过将原始两个变量放入数组中来重新分配值，但相反 命令你
probably almost never do that but you might be able to use it to impress
可能几乎永远不会这样做，但有一天你可能会用它
someone on a technical interview someday the other thing i wanted to show you is
在技术面试中给某人留下深刻印象我想向你展示的另一件事是，当你运行 match 函数时
that destructuring can also be used with regular expressions
，解构也可以与正则表达式一起使用
when you run the match function on a string it returns an array of results
一个字符串，它返回一个结果数组，
you can then easily provide descriptive variable names for the regular
然后您可以轻松地为正则表达式匹配提供描述性变量名称，
expression matches that's cool but i have one last thing to
这很酷，但我还有最后一件事要
mention imagine you want to destructure an object
提到，假设您想解构一个对象，
but you don't know the property name until runtime you can use computed
但直到运行时您才知道属性名称 可以
properties in destructuring just like you can with object literals
在解构中使用计算属性，就像使用对象文字一样，
by wrapping a property name in brackets it now takes a variable as its value
通过将属性名称包装在括号中它现在需要一个 变量作为它的值
instead of a static name in other words it's computed at runtime
而不是静态名称，换句话说，它是在运行时计算的，
which you can then follow with a colon to provide it with a static variable
然后你可以用冒号为它提供一个静态变量
name to use in your code and that's pretty much everything i know about
名称以在你的代码中使用，这几乎就是我所知道的关于
destructuring
解构的一切